<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools" tools:ignore="MissingTranslation">
    <string name="header_disclaimer">Disclaimer</string>
    <string name="disclaimer">
QMobile\'s sustainability and success rely heavily on customer satisfaction, and therefore we are committed to providing the best products and services to our customers.\n\n
QApp Store is an application market designed to enhance your mobile phone experience where numerous applications and games are available for download.\n\n
In order to use QApp Store, you must be 13 years of age or older or have permission from your parent or legal guardian to access the QApp Store.\n\n
In order to access QApp Store, you may be required to provide information about yourself such as your name, address, and billing details.  The information that you provide must always be accurate, correct and up to date.  QMobile will take all reasonable steps to preserve and protect user data in accordance with Pakistani Laws.  QMobile reserves the right to use the meta-data and other user information and also share this with third parties except as may be specifically restricted.  The user’s submission of information and data constitutes acceptance of the terms stated hereinabove regarding use of the data and information by QMobile.\n\n
QMobile is not responsible for the content in the applications. You understand that all content which you may access through such third party applications are the sole responsibility of the owners of the applications and that QMobile is not liable for any loss or damage that you may experience as a result of the use of any of those third party applications.\n\n
"Intellectual Property Rights" means any and all rights under patent law, copyright law, trade secret law, trademark law, and any and all other proprietary rights. You agree that the owners of the applications own all legal right, title and interest in and to the applications, logo design and, websites including any Intellectual Property Rights.\n\n
You should be aware that the content offered to you through third party application may be protected by intellectual property rights.  Complete or partial reproduction and use of these objects is not permitted without prior expressed written consent of the owner.  You may not modify, rent, lease, loan, sell, distribute or create derivative works based on these data, content, or resources (either in whole or in part) unless you have been specifically given permission to do so by the relevant owners.\n\n
Any or all damage caused to the hardware and/or data caused by the use or download of any of the applications is of no responsibility of QMobile.\n\n
Download or use of some applications may be associated with additional costs that should be end user responsibility which you will need to check and comply with before downloading apps/games.\n\n
Prices and availability of all the Applications in QApp Store are subject to change at any time before you enter into the contract by clicking on the “install” button.\n\n
The same terms and conditions and the end user responsibilities apply to all the applications including music, games, videos, news and books.\n\n
The contents in the Applications and games are not of any responsibility of QMobile and are not liable for any material that you may find offending or derogatory.\n\n
You expressly understand and agree that your use of the QApp store is at your sole risk.  Your use of the QApp store and any material downloaded or otherwise obtained through the use of the QApp store is at your own discretion and risk and you are solely responsible for any damage to your mobile phone or loss of data that results from such use.\n\n
QMobile accepts no liability and will not be liable for any loss or damage arising directly or indirectly from use of the applications, including and not limited to, any defect, error, imperfection, fault, mistake or inaccuracy of the applications or due to unavailability of the applications.\n\n
You expressly understand and agree that QMobile, its subsidiaries and affiliates, and its licensors shall not be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, consequential or exemplary damages that may be incurred by you, including any loss of data, whether or not QMobile or its representatives have been advised of or should have been aware of the possibility of any such losses arising.\n\n
To the maximum extent permitted by law, you agree to defend, indemnify and hold QMobile harmless, its affiliates and their respective directors, officers, employees and agents from and against any and all claims, actions, suits or proceedings, as well as any and all losses, liabilities, damages, costs and expenses arising out from your use of the QApp Store and accept all responsibility regarding submission of data including private information.\n\n
    </string>

</resources>